Finding Aid for the Anthony C. Beilenson Papers LSC.0391
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Press relations / Media activities
  - Newspaper clippings
    - Gas tax
      - For the date noted (Box 427, Folder 5)
    - Gay rights
      - For the dates noted (Box 430, Folder 12)
    - General
      - For the year noted. f.1 of 3 (Box 427, Folder 7)
        Letters, notes, transcripts
      - For the year noted. f.2 of 3 (Box 427, Folder 8)
        Clippings (newsprint). f.1 of 2
      - For the year noted. f.3 of 3 (Box 427, Folder 9)
        Clippings (newsprint). f.2 of 2
      - For the year noted. f.1 of 3 (Box 427, Folder 11)
      - For the year noted. f.2 of 3 (Box 427, Folder 12)
      - For the year noted. f.3 of 3 (Box 427, Folder 13)
      - For the year noted. f.1 of 3 (Box 428, Folder 1)
        Letters, notes
      - For the year noted. f.2 of 3 (Box 428, Folder 2)
      - For the year noted. f.3 of 3 (Box 428, Folder 3)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 3 (Box 428, Folder 4)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 3 (Box 428, Folder 5)
      - For the date noted. f.3 of 3 (Box 428, Folder 6)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 428, Folder 7)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 428, Folder 8)
      - For the date noted (Box 428, Folder 9)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 428, Folder 10)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 428, Folder 11)
      - For the date noted (Box 429, Folder 1)
      - For the date noted (Box 429, Folder 2)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 429, Folder 3)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 429, Folder 4)
      - For the date noted (Box 429, Folder 5)
      - For the date noted (Box 429, Folder 6)
      - For the dates noted (Box 430, Folder 1)
      - For the dates noted (Box 430, Folder 5)
      - For the dates noted (Box 430, Folder 13)
      - Including campaign. For the date noted. f.1 of 4 (Box 430, Folder 21)
      - Including campaign. For the date noted. f.2 of 4 (Box 431, Folder 1)
      - Including campaign. For the date noted. f.3 of 4 (Box 431, Folder 2)
      - Including campaign. For the date noted. f.4 of 4 (Box 431, Folder 3)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 431, Folder 5)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 431, Folder 6)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 431, Folder 7)
        Clippings (photocopies)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 431, Folder 8)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 3 (Box 432, Folder 9)
        Notes, photocopies
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 3 (Box 432, Folder 10)
        Clippings (newsprint). F.1 of 2
      - For the date noted. f.3 of 3 (Box 432, Folder 11)
        Clippings (newsprint). F.2 of 2
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 4 (Box 433, Folder 1)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 4 (Box 433, Folder 2)
      - For the date noted. f.3 of 4 (Box 433, Folder 3)
      - For the date noted. f.4 of 4 (Box 433, Folder 4)
    - God votes
      - For the year noted (Box 427, Folder 10)
    - Gulf War
      - For the date noted (Box 431, Folder 4)
    - Immigration
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 432, Folder 1)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 432, Folder 2)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 434, Folder 1)
        Memos, clippings (photocopies)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 434, Folder 2)
      - For the date noted (Box 434, Folder 5)
      - For the date noted (Box 434, Folder 6)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 435)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 435)
    - Letters
      - For the date noted (Box 435)
    - Letters to editors
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 434, Folder 9)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 434, Folder 10)
    - Local
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 432, Folder 3)
        Memos, notes, clippings (photocopies)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 432, Folder 4)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 3 (Box 434, Folder 11)
        Notes, newsletters, clippings (photocopies)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 3 (Box 434, Folder 12)
      - For the date noted. f.3 of 3 (Box 434, Folder 13)
      - For the date noted (Box 435)
    - Los Angeles issues
      - For the dates noted (Box 430, Folder 8)
      - For the dates noted (Box 430, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous
      - For the date noted (Box 432, Folder 8)
    - National
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 432, Folder 5)
        Newsletters, clippings (photocopies)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 432, Folder 6)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 435)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 435)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 435)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 435)
    - Op ed
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 432, Folder 13)
        ACB / Sybert op eds. LA Times / Valley. Clippings (newsprint)
    - Op eds
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 432, Folder 12)
        ACB / Sybert op eds. LA Times / Valley. Notes, clippings (photocopies)
    - Personal
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 435)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 435)
    - Pesticide controls
      - For the date noted (Box 427, Folder 4)
    - Political
      - For the dates noted (Box 430, Folder 3)
      - For the dates noted (Box 430, Folder 9)
      - For the dates noted (Box 430, Folder 18)
      - For the date noted (Box 432, Folder 7)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 4 (Box 433, Folder 5)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 4 (Box 433, Folder 6)
      - For the date noted. f.3 of 4 (Box 433, Folder 7)
      - For the date noted. f.4 of 4 (Box 433, Folder 8)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 435)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 435)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 435)
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 435)
    - Point Mugu
      - For the date noted (Box 434, Folder 17)
    - Reapportionment
      - For the date noted (Box 430, Folder 19)
    - Reproductive choice
      - For the date noted (Box 430, Folder 14)
    - Retirement
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 435)
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 435)
    - Santa Monica Mountain bill
      - For the dates noted (Box 430, Folder 2)
      - For the dates noted (Box 430, Folder 10)
    - Santa Monica Mountains
      - For the dates noted (Box 430, Folder 20)
      - For the date noted (Box 434, Folder 16)
    - Teenage pregnancy
      - For the date noted (Box 430, Folder 4)
      - For the dates noted (Box 430, Folder 11)
    - Tobacco advertising
      - For the date noted (Box 426, Folder 16)
- Press relations / Media activities
  - Newspaper clippings
    - Consumer protection
      - For the date noted (Box 426, Folder 14)
    - Creation
      - KNXT editorial (Box 426, Folder 15)
        Transcript
    - General
      - For the date noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 426, Folder 5)
        Letters, etc
      - For the date noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 426, Folder 6)
      - For the dates noted. F.1 of 2 (Box 426, Folder 7)
      - For the dates noted. F.2 of 2 (Box 426, Folder 8)
    - Lead based paint
      - For the date noted (Box 426, Folder 11)
    - Noise pollution
      - For the dates noted (Box 426, Folder 9)
    - Odometers
      - For the dates noted. F.1 of 2 (Box 426, Folder 12)
    - Odometers
      - For the dates noted. F.2 of 2 (Box 426, Folder 13)
    - Organ transplants
      - For the date noted (Box 426, Folder 10)
  - Photographs
    - ACB
      - Legislative (Box 191, Folder 2)
      - With constituents and political supporters (Box 191, Folder 3)
      - With national leaders (Box 191, Folder 4)
        Includes photographs with President Jimmy Carter and White House staff transmittal letters
      - With foreign leaders (Box 191, Folder 5)
        With: King Hussein of Jordan, Menachem Begin, Moshe Dayan, the Dalai Lama, Kurt Waldheim, etc
      - Portraits (Box 191, Folder 6)
      - Legislative (Box 191, Folder 7)
      - With national leaders (Box 191, Folder 8)
      - With constituents and political supporters (Box 191, Folder 9)
      - With foreign leaders [no photos filed] (Box 191, Folder 10)
        [No photographs transferred?]
      - Legislative (Box 191, Folder 11)
      - With constituents and political supporters (Box 191, Folder 12)
      - With national leaders (Box 191, Folder 13)
        With: Governor Jerry Brown and Speaker O'Neill
      - With foreign leaders [no photos filed] (Box 191, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 191, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 191, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 191, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 191, Folder 18)
        An extensive file. Includes lists, cover sheets, etc. Includes photos with: President George H.W. Bush
      - Miscellaneous (Box 191, Folder 19)
        An extensive file. Includes lists, cover sheets, etc. Includes photo with: President George H.W. Bush
      - Miscellaneous 93 - 94. f.1 of 2 (Box 192, Folder 1)
        An extensive file
      - Miscellaneous 93 - 94. f.2 of 2 (Box 192, Folder 2)
        An extensive file. Includes photo of Mr. and Mrs. Beilenson with President and Mrs. Clinton (decorated tree in background at White House? formal wear)
      - Duplicates of photos sent to Rick Taylor (Box 192, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 192, Folder 4)
        Includes photos with: Menachem Begin, VP Al Gore
      - Photo inventories 1992 (and past) (Box 192, Folder 5)
      - Portraits. With President Clinton (Box 192, Folder 6)
        Also with Mrs. Clinton
      - Portraits. Used for mailing (Box 192, Folder 7)
        Includes sleeved photograph used for an exhibit: Roosevelt Rees Beilenson / Vote the straight Democratic ticket [sign on headquarters]
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 8)
        Color. Also color snapshots of man and woman in East Indian dress?
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 9)
        Black and white
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 10)
        Noted: discolored (black and white). Date as noted on folder, but would seem to be the same as previous, also identified elsewhere as 1992 Jul
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 11)
        Color
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 12)
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 13)
        Black and white. Duplicates from previous folder
      - Portraits [presiding over House] (Box 192, Folder 14)
        Photocopies (from television)
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 15)
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 16)
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 17)
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 18)
        Black and white. Prints and proofs
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 19)
        Black and white. Also negatives, copies of previously filed photographs?
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 20)
        Noted "bad"
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 21)
        Noted "good." Some negatives, cf. photos in previous folders
      - Portraits [speaking] (Box 192, Folder 22)
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 23)
        Black and white proofs
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 24)
        At Solstice Canyon. Color
      - Portraits (Box 192, Folder 25)
        Black and white. Cf. copies filed elsewhere
    - ACB - Assemblyman / senator
      - Various transmittal letters (Box 196, Folder 11)
        Removed from items enclosed when filed by ACB
    - ACB - Assemblyman
      - With various persons, primarily unidentified (Box 194, Folder 15)
        Black and white. Includes photos with: Martin Luther King, 1968, with President Gerald Ford (color), with Governor Pat Brown, campaign signs, etc
      - With various persons, primarily unidentified (Box 194, Folder 16)
        Black and white. Also some negatives. Includes campaign photographs, portraits by Pope Studios
      - With various persons, primarily unidentified (Box 194, Folder 17)
        Black and white. Includes photos with: Coretta King
      - With various persons, primarily unidentified (Box 195, Folder 1)
        Black and white. Oversize proofs removed to Box _____
      - With various persons, primarily unidentified (Box 195, Folder 2)
        Black and white. Also proofs and negatives
      - With various persons, primarily unidentified (Box 195, Folder 3)
        Black and white. Includes photos of Dolores with: Alan Cranston, Gov Pat Brown
      - Portraits (primarily) and with various persons (Box 195, Folder 4)
        Black and white. Includes pencil drawing signed "Hair"
      - Portraits (primarily) and with various persons (Box 195, Folder 5)
        Black and white. Includes photos with Henry Waxman
    - ACB - Assemblyman / senator
      - Portraits and with various persons (Box 195, Folder 6)
        Black and white. Proofs and prints
      - Portraits (Box 195, Folder 7)
        Black and white. Proofs and prints. Pope Studios
      - Portraits (Box 195, Folder 8)
        Black and white. Proofs and prints. Includes photo of office as senator
      - Portrait (Box 195, Folder 9)
        Black and white copy of drawing. Negative and print. Negative labeled San Diego Union
      - Portrait (Box 196, Folder 1)
        Black and white. Negatives, proofs, prints. With transmittal letter from Stanley Evans
      - Portraits (Box 196, Folder 2)
      - Portraits (Box 196, Folder 3)
        Black and white. Seemingly from bill signing ceremony. Also proofs with transmittal letter from United Press International, Charles J. Gibbs photographer?
      - Portraits (Box 196, Folder 4)
        Black and white. Negatives and proofs
      - With various persons (Box 196, Folder 5)
      - With various persons (Box 196, Folder 6)
        Black and white. Includes photo with: Yitzhak Rabin, Jack Lemmon
      - UCLA Distinguished Lectureship (Box 196, Folder 7)
        Black and white. Includes transmittal letter from Raymond D. Goodman, M.D
      - Portraits (Box 196, Folder 8)
        Black and white. Negatives only, various sizes. One color slide
      - Portraits (Box 196, Folder 9)
        Black and white. Includes photograph with Dolores Beilenson, photo of building with painted sign: Democratic headquarters / Rees Congress / Beilenson [state] Senate / Sieroty Assembly
      - Portrait (Box 196, Folder 10)
        Color slides
    - ACB at events
      - Tree planting ceremony (Box 193, Folder 61)
        Color snapshots. "KVH [unidentified] sent these photos"
      - Groundbreaking, unidentified (Box 193, Folder 62)
        Color negatives
      - AIDS Walk Los Angeles (Box 193, Folder 63)
      - ACB, Braude, and others, Tarzana P.O. (Box 193, Folder 64)
      - Events (Box 193, Folder 65)
        Color snapshots, unidentified
      - ACB with Braude, others, Barrington Park (Box 193, Folder 66)
      - ACB breakfast (Box 193, Folder 67)
      - Senior citizens center event [unidentified] (Box 194, Folder 1)
      - Orange [grove] event (Box 194, Folder 2)
      - Fundraiser (Box 194, Folder 3)
      - Town hall (Box 194, Folder 4)
      - Picnic (Box 194, Folder 5)
      - Open house (Box 194, Folder 6)
      - Academy Day (Box 194, Folder 7)
      - Rockwell tour (Box 194, Folder 8)
        Color. Also transmittal letters, Rockwell report
      - Artist Discovery (Box 194, Folder 9)
      - Volunteer breakfast (Box 194, Folder 10)
        Black and white. Negatives and small prints
      - Gregory Peck party (Box 194, Folder 11)
      - Los Angeles World Affairs Council (Box 194, Folder 12)
      - Paramount Ranch picnic (Box 194, Folder 13)
      - Picnic in Santa Monica mountains (Box 194, Folder 14)
    - ACB lists
      - Photo inventories (Box 191, Folder 1)
        Various lists, not tied to these boxes and folders, but should give indication of where to look in files
    - ACB with others
      - With Perez family (Box 193, Folder 32)
      - With intern Yoeli Barag (Box 193, Folder 33)
      - With Herschel [Heschel?] Day School students (Box 193, Folder 34)
      - Speaking to summer interns (Box 193, Folder 35)
      - With group of women (Box 193, Folder 36)
      - With students from Hamilton High School (Box 193, Folder 37)
      - Speaking to USC students (Box 193, Folder 38)
      - With high school students from Spokane (Box 193, Folder 39)
      - At Elephant bill hearing (Box 193, Folder 40)
      - With University High School students (Box 193, Folder 41)
      - ACB in committee (Box 193, Folder 42)
        Black and white. Noted as "recent"
      - With 2 AIPAC members (Box 193, Folder 43)
      - With Close Up students at capitol (Box 193, Folder 45)
      - With pro Israel PAC (Box 193, Folder 46)
      - With seated woman in office (Box 193, Folder 47)
        Black and white. Canoga Park High School / University High School student with Close Up program
      - With staff [no photo filed] (Box 193, Folder 48)
        [Folder empty when transferred]
      - With Harvard student in office (Box 193, Folder 49)
      - With Close Up students in Washington, D.C (Box 193, Folder 50)
        Black and white. Cf. photographs filed elsewhere
      - Outside California state Capitol (Box 193, Folder 51)
      - With group, Jewish Family Service building (Box 193, Folder 52)
      - With group outside. Pacific Palisades Democratic Club (Box 193, Folder 53)
      - With various people outside. Event unidentified (Box 193, Folder 54)
        Black and white. Persons identified on verso
      - With John Rhonde (?) and Dan Akaka (?) (Box 193, Folder 55)
        Black and white. Handwriting of identification unclear
      - At campaign headquarters (Box 193, Folder 56)
      - With Western Los Angeles Chamber of Commerce (Box 193, Folder 57)
        Black and white. Also 2 color snapshot prints
      - With Dolores and contributors (Box 193, Folder 58)
        Black and white. Proofs and prints. With:Marianne Chalker, Sheldon Andelson (gay rights activist), Doris and Larry Silverton, and unidentified
      - ACB in committee (Box 193, Folder 59)
      - ACB staff, old (Box 193, Folder 60)
        Black and white. Prints and proofs. Also 8 x 10 negative
    - ACB with personalities
      - With Steve Afriat (Box 193, Folder 1)
      - With James Baker (Box 193, Folder 2)
      - With Brent Blackwater (Box 193, Folder 3)
      - With Derek Bok and Claude Pepper (Box 193, Folder 4)
      - With Bruce Burton, Spain (Box 193, Folder 5)
      - With George H.W. Bush (Box 193, Folder 6)
      - With Alfredo Cristiani (of El Salvador) (Box 193, Folder 7)
      - With Tony Coelho and others (Box 193, Folder 8)
      - With George Dukakis (Box 193, Folder 9)
      - With SS Endeavor crew (Box 193, Folder 10)
      - With John Tunney (Box 193, Folder 11)
      - With Amin Gemayel, president of Lebanon (Box 193, Folder 12)
      - With Dick Gephardt (Box 193, Folder 13)
      - Dolores Beilenson with Joanne Kemp and Shcharansky (Box 193, Folder 14)
      - With Larry Kimbell and Elwin Svenson (Box 193, Folder 15)
      - With Joan Mondale, Walter Mondale (Box 193, Folder 16)
        Black and white, color. Black and white with Walter Mondale 1980s
      - With Hosni Mubarak (Box 193, Folder 17)
        Black and white, color
      - With Congressman Natcher (Box 193, Folder 18)
      - With Leon Panetta (Box 193, Folder 19)
      - With Claude Pepper (Box 193, Folder 20)
      - With Shimon Peres (Box 193, Folder 21)
      - With Joy Picus and others (Box 193, Folder 22)
      - With George Schultz (Box 193, Folder 23)
        Color, black and white
      - With Gen Norman Schwarzkopf, others (Box 193, Folder 24)
      - With Anatoly Scharansky (Box 193, Folder 25)
      - ACB and Dolores with Vladimir Slepak (Box 193, Folder 26)
      - With Deng Xiaoping (Box 193, Folder 27)
      - With Zev Yaroslavsky (Box 193, Folder 28)
      - With Andrew Young (Box 193, Folder 29)
      - With movie and music stars (Box 193, Folder 30)
        Black and white. Lists photos not present in file (e.g., with Carol Channing). Includes with: Jean Stapleton, Roberta Flack. Includes note from Henry Waxman re photos of Jean Stapleton, Norman Lear
      - With Henry Waxman? and others (Box 193, Folder 31)
        Color. [Not in folder]
  - Press files
    - Articles about ACB
      - For the dates noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 438)
      - For the dates noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 438)
        First folder includes master list
    - Constituent mailings
      - For the dates noted. F.3 of 3 (Box 437)
      - For the dates noted. F.2 of 3 (Box 437)
      - For the dates noted. F.1 of 3 (Box 437)
        Also master list
    - Editorials / columns
      - For the years noted. f.1 of 2 (Box 424, Folder 21)
        Letters to the editor, with copies of correspondence, clippings or photocopies of printed letters, etc
      - For the years noted. f.2 of 2 (Box 424, Folder 22)
    - Press releases
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 1)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 2)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 3)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 4)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 5)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 6)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 7)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 8)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 9)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 10)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 11)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 12)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 13)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 14)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 15)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 16)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 17)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 18)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 19)
      - For the year noted (Box 424, Folder 20)
  - Press releases
    - Biographies
      - For the dates noted (Box 437)
  - Radio
    - Transcript
      - ACB Democratic radio address (Box 425, Folder 2)
        Reagan arms to Iran
      - ACB KGIL radio (Box 425, Folder 3)
    - Transcripts
      - ACB KCRW radio (Box 424, Folder 23)
        Master list and transcripts
      - ACB KCRW radio (Box 425, Folder 1)
        Master list and transcript
- State
  - Campaign
    - General. f.1 of 2 (Box 471)
    - Endorsements (Box 471)
    - General. f.2 of 2 (Box 471)
    - Letters to people lists (Box 471)
    - Opponents' publicity. f.2 of 2 (Box 471)
    - HQs and workers (Box 471)
    - Materials. f.1 of 2 (Box 471)
    - Materials. f.2 of 2 (Box 471)
    - Materials (Box 471)
    - Opponents' publicity. f.1 of 2 (Box 471)
    - Bulk permit 824 (Box 471)
    - Campaign ideas. f.2 of 2 (Box 472)
    - Fundraising. f.1 of 3 (Box 472)
      Contact lists
    - Fundraising. f.2 of 3 (Box 472)
    - Fundraising. f.3 of 3 (Box 472)
    - Campaign director. f.1 of 2 (Box 472)
    - Campaign director. f.2 of 2 (Box 472)
    - Miscellaneous f.1 of 2 (Box 472)
      Contact lists, photograph
    - Miscellaneous f.2 of 2 (Box 472)
      Newspapers
    - Campaign ideas. f.1 of 2 (Box 472)
    - Support correspondence (Box 473, Folder 1)
    - Riverside and San Bernardino Counties (Box 473, Folder 2)
    - San Diego County (Box 473, Folder 3)
    - San Luis Obispo and Santa Barbara Counties (Box 473, Folder 4)
    - 24th C.D (Box 473, Folder 5)
    - 22nd C.D (Box 473, Folder 6)
    - 28th C.D (Box 473, Folder 7)
    - 31st C.D (Box 473, Folder 8)
    - 32nd C.D (Box 473, Folder 9)
    - Orange County (Box 473, Folder 10)
    - Speeches (Box 473, Folder 11)
      ACB statements and press releases
    - General (Box 473, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (Box 473, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 473, Folder 14)
    - Fliers (Box 473, Folder 15)
    - Clipping (Los Angeles Times) (Box 473, Folder 16)
    - Contributions (Box 473, Folder 17)
      List of contributors, correspondence
    - Finances (Box 473, Folder 18)
    - Contributions (Box 473, Folder 19)
  - Legislative
    - Correspondence
      - A.B. 1616 - Fluoridation (against). f.3 of 3 (Box 520)
      - A.B. 1616 - Fluoridation (against). f.2 of 3 (Box 520)